The Last Outlaw is a tv movie, action, western film directed by Geoff Murphy.
The story follows a band of former Confederate
soldiers who were part of a cavalry unit.
Their commander, Graff, had once been a heroic and staunch supporter of the Southern
cause, but after losing his family, he became coldhearted and ruthless.
His second-in-command is Eustis, whom Graff has trained on the
strategies of leadership and combat command.
Graff, played by Mickey Rourke.
Eustis, played by Dermot Mulroney.
Potts, played by Ted Levine.
Wills, played by John C. McGinley.
Philo, played by Steve Buscemi.
Lovecraft, played by Keith David.
The Last Outlaw is a 1993 American Western television film starring Mickey Rourke, Dermot
Mulroney, Ted Levine, Daniel Quinn, Gavan O'Herlihy, Keith David, John C.
McGinley, and Steve Buscemi, along with a variety of other known actors,
which has since become a cult classic among Western genre fans.
It was directed by Geoff Murphy and written by Eric Red.
It was initially broadcast on HBO on October 30, 1993.
The film explores themes of psychopath, bank robber, river battle.